

Pranav Maheshwari

Senior Product Engineer - QA



Summary

Quality Analyst with 2.5+ years experience in Testing.

Expertise in STLC, Agile Process, Test Management, API Testing along with basic knowledge of Automation Testing using Selenium.

Wanting to be the part of the team where I may be able to provide the company with the benefit of my knowledge and skills and towards the achievement of goal which in the process will satisfy my craving for learning



Experience

Nov 2018 present

Senior Product Engineer QA

ezDI Healthcare Data Intelligence

- · Responsible for creation of API Framework
- Responsible for API Testing using RestAssured in JAVA as well as Postman
- · Responsible for handling all the product knowledge sessions for Jr. QAs.
- Responsible for performing Performance & Security Testing using ZAP

Jul 2018 -Oct 2018

Product Engineer QA

VVDN Technologies

- · Responsible for preparation of SRS as per client requirements
- · Responsible for creation of Test cases and executing them.
- · Performing IOT and Embedded device testing.
- · Responsible for handling all the CR from clients.
- · Involved in client interaction, scrum and spring meetings.
- · Well versed with AI driven IOT testing.

Jun 2017 -Jun 2018

Associate Product Engineer - QA

ezDI Healhcare Data Intelligence

- · Responsible for creating Test cases and executing them.
- Well versed with Test Management tools such as Jira, Clickup and testlink.
- · Performing Manual Testing, Performance Testing, API Testing.
- · Responsible for executing the automated tests.
- · Involved in Daily Scrum Meetings & Sprint Meetings.
- · Experienced in Agile Scrum Model



Education

Jun 2013 -Jun 2017

Government Engineering College, Gandhinagar

- · Bachelor of Engineering , Computers.
- Passed with distinction 8.61 CGPA



Phone

+91-9979970057

E-mail

pranavmaheshwari7@gmail.com

Date of birth

June 08, 1995

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pranavs maheshwari/



Manual Testing

Automation Testing

Selenium & TestNG

Java

JIRA, ClickUp

Testlink

Performance Testing - Load Runner (Basic)

API Testing -RestAssured, Postman

Jenkins

Html / CSS, Js, Bootstap

MYSOL

Amazon Web Service



Interests

Instruments: Guitar & Piano

Sports : Cricket & Volleyball

Writing (Articles , Poems , Short

Stories etc.)

Learning New Technologies & stuffs.



Certificates | Awards

Employee of the year - 2019

HIPAA Basics

HIPAA Privacy Rule

HIPAA Security Rule

HIPAA for Business Associates

Kubernetes Basics